[{"answer": "Sure, there's always a moment for anybody.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "Has there been a moment when you could have veered down the Charlie Sheen route?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Terrific.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "Matt Damon, how are you?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, this is a -- you know, my mother is a professor of early childhood education.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "What would you make him do?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "We are the people who make sure things happen according to plan.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Who the hell are you guys?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Now that is the moment in the movie when you kind of realized life is not going to be quite the same again, isn't it?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "No, what -- what I actually said was, I thought of a really reasonable thing at the time.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Has she gotten more dangerous as the last two years have progressed?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I disagree with her politically.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "What do you think of her now?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I didn't.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "You didn't watch \"Sarah Palin in Alaska\"?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Are you a fan?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I did not.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Did you start a small business with your tax break?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Again, does that come back to your sort of slightly disillusioned view of Obama, that when you voted for audacity of hope it wouldn't have been giving the rich tax breaks and watching 10 percent of your population remain unemployed?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Oh, man.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Have we still got hope, you think?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "When I hear you speak like this, I mean, the obvious question to ask you is, do you have political aspiration at all?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, I'm really interested in politics.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "And if not, why don't you?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, the thing is with water there's not like -- there's not a magic bullet.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "What's the single most effective thing you could do with that if you had your adjustment bureau hat on?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "There's no adjustment bureau in the world that -- yes, you know, it is very challenging and very fun to have four girls.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "If you had the power to have some kind of control over your four daughters, would you take it?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Well, the first thing he said the first day I met him was don't let them keep you inside.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "I mean if you were advising a young guy who had a big hit movie, what did George say to you?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Physically don't -- just because they're -- the celebrity can feel a little oppressive.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "By that you mean physically in your home?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, the work part, yes.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Do you think, wow, this is what I've lived for, this moment?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Because I've got the most amazing family, and I've got the most amazing wife.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "And why did you think that?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Sure, there's always a moment for anybody.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Has there been a moment when you could have veered down the Charlie Sheen route?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "No, and my parents didn't encourage me to -- well, they didn't discourage me from being an actor.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Would you encourage a daughter of yours to be an actress?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "It just seems funny to me to talk about --", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "I mean, when I say superstar, how do you react to that phrase?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "To me, yes.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Is it ludicrous?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Because you're really -- you're Matt Damon, you're a human being, right?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "The best answer I ever heard to that was George.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "How do you stay normal?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Well, we don't live in Hollywood.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "What's the secret to a successful marriage in Hollywood?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "I'm sure I'm not.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Are you easy to live with?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "You got a two-week rule?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "You aren't allowed to be apart for more than two weeks?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I was basically George in \"Up in the Air.\"", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Like George in \"Up in the Air\"?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "You have.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "I have?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I think he's a terrific actor.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I was -- this is funny because my wife and I -- this is going to sound like I'm blowing smoke but we were sitting in bed watching PIERS", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "That's pretty high praise, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I really hope so.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Will there be a fourth \"Bourne\"?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "With Paul.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "With Paul Greengrass?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Well, we just would have written another movie and gone and done it, which is what Ben did do.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Do you ever think, what would I have done?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Well, my hope is to start directing.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Who would be the leading man, leading lady, producer, director?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Well, Chris Moore, who produced \"Good Will Hunting,\" my old friend, Chris and John Gordon, those guys.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Who's the producer?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Oh, I mean, it always depends on the job.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Leading man, leading lady?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Ben would be my leading man.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Ben's the leading man?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "I wouldn't do too bad with Emily Blunt.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Leading lady?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "I have no idea, but I'm dying to find out.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What would Emily say, do you think?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I would love to find out.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Should we find out?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "We're being chased.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What's happening to me?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Might infuse some women into \"The Adjustment Bureau.\"", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "What would you do?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "-- flying the sisterhood flag now.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I agree with you that it's hard not to sound pageantesque when you answer this.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "What would it be?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Well, I said, that is exactly it.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Isn't that it?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I left home at a very young age.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "If you had that power?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I wouldn't.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "If you hadn't made the sacrifices, would you be sitting here now as the star of a big movie?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Boy, I -- I kind of wonder what the next moment is.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "What would be the moment, Matt?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Working with Emily Blunt.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "What about professionally for you?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "You know, I -- I would relive -- right now -- I would relive all four years of college in ten minutes.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "What would be the moment you'd relive?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "You have nothing.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Is it because you don't have any responsibilities?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm going to bring it down now.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "What about you, John?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "So what are the faults of Mr. Perfect?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Yes, he did do that.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "Did you do that?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "I did my first job with Judi Dench.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "How important is humor on the sets of these things?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "No, I'm kidding.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Are you in it?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "Jesse Owens, working on it, trying to get it made.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "Jesse Owens I'm hearing?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "I got old, man.", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "What happened to you?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "I'm about to start a film in march called \"Lupo.\"", "docId": "110303pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "What are you up to next?", "qSentId": 743}]